Baruch, Ismar Compilation of U.S. Employment Service and U.S. Civil Service Documents 6099
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Democracy and Bureaucracy, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 67)
  Hyman G. Rickover. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. December 7, 1963. Symposium Sponsored by The Fund for the Republic, Inc.
- Administration, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 68)
  Four Lectures by Outstanding Leaders in the Management Field. Delivered in the Graduate School of Agriculture. U.S. Department of Agriculture. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. February 22-23, 1939.
- The Personnel Program of the United States Department of Agriculture, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 69)
  by Roy F. Hendrickson. Pamphlet no.15 October 1939. Published by Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library.
- Government Careers for College Graduates, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 70)
  Leonard D. White. An Experiment of the Selection of Federal Employees from Liberal Arts Colleges. Civil Service Assembly, Pamphlet no.5 U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. June, 1937.
- Report of Research Program for Special Conference, 1924 (Box 46, Folder 71)
  Methods of Measured Personnel Effort by W.W. Charters and I. B. Whitley. American Management Association. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. Research Bureau for Retail Training. University of Pittsburgh.
- Federal Conference on Employee-Management Relations, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 72)
  U.S. Civil Services Commission. Mach 1966.
- Recruitment of Science and Engineering Graduates for the Federal Service, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 73)
  U.S. Interdepartmental committee on scientific research and development. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. December 1952.
- Statement Before the House Committee on Civil Service, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 74)
  Harold D. Smith. April 14, 1943. Concerning Government Problems of Personnel and Management. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library.
- Perspectives and Prospects in Personnel Management, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 75)
  Address by the honorable Rocco C. Siciliano. Special Assistance to the President for Personnel Management Before the Society for Personnel Administration. Washington, D.C. June 3, 1958. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library.
- Personnel Administration in the U.S. Department of Agriculture as Viewed from this Departmental View, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 76)
  remarks of Henry F. Shepherd. Chief, Personnel Operations Division. U.S. Department of Agriculture. Before the Training in Administration Management Leadership Workshop. Huron, South Dakota. December 3, 1958.
- A Guide to College Recruitment, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 77)
  Pamphlet no.12. Society for Personnel Administration. Prepared by a Work Group of the Society for Personnel Administration. Washington 15, D.C. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. July, 1956.
- The Federal Executive, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 78)
  Graduate School U.S. Department of Agriculture. By Ralph S. Roberts, Administrative Assistant Secretary of Agriculture. Final Address of the First Management Development Program For New Federal Executives. Marriot Moto Hotel. April 26, 1960.
- Government Administration in Management Development Programs, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 79)
  by Bernard J. James and Frank X. Steggert. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. September 6, 1962.
- The Recruitment of Engineers for the Federal Classified Civil Service, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 80)
  Presented by Ernest J. Socking, principal Examiner (Engineering) of the U.S. Civil Service Commission before the engineering deans of land grant colleges at Washington, D.C. November 1939.
- Classification: U.S. Civil Service Commission Personnel Classification Division, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 81)
  Address by Ismar Baruch. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. May 22, 1941.
- Memorandum Prepared at Mr. Macy's Suggestion as a Comment on a Personal Letter Decrying the Present Situation of the Classification Act and its Administration, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 82)
  U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. Ismar Baruch. 1954.
- The Federal Position Classification Program in the European Theatre, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 83)
  R.J. Novogod. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. 1947.
- Need for Keeping Position-Classification Plans Current, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 84)
  Ismar Baruch. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. 1951.
- Civil Service in Britain, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 85)
  Don K. Price. 1937. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library.
- Historical Epitome: Personnel Research Federation, 1924 (Box 46, Folder 86)
  U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. June 7, 1924.
- Health Protection for Operators of VDTs/GRTs, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 87)
  Witten by Tobi Bergman. Copyright 1980. The New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, Inc. (NYCOSH). Office of Personnel Management Library.
- A Study of the Practice of Substituting Perience for Education, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 88)
  As Requirement for Entrance to Civil Service Examinations. By Ruth Anne Winslow. Submitted as a Record of Independent Work in Political Science. Goucher College. June 1945.
- Bette Personal Management in the Federal Government, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 89)
  Raymond R. Zimmerman, Past President, Society for the Advancement of Management and until recently Administrative Assistance to the President. August 5, 1947.
- Characteristics of Successful Executives, 1932 (Box 46, Folder 90)
  Human Engineering Laboratory. Johnson O'Connor. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. March 12, 1937.
- Civil Service Systems of Foreign Countries, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  U.S. Commission on organization of the executive branch of the government. Personnel task force. Staff memorandum. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. July 22, 1954.
- Ove Fifty Years in the Federal Government, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  and the Public Utility Corporation by W.L. Pepperman. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library, January 29, 1954.
- Ismar Baruch Doodles: The Pendleton Room Collection, 1941-1946 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  U.S. Civil Service Commission Washington, D.C. 1941-1946.
- The Meaning of Responsibility in the Public Service, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  William D. Carey. Executive Assistant Director. Bureau of the Budget. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. May 6, 1966.
- Statement of a General Policy For Providing Non-Housekeeping Quarters to Civilian Hospital Employees, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  U.S. President 1933-1945 (Franklin D. Roosevelt). July 11, 1941.
- Goals for Federal Managers, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  Executive Office of the President Bureau of the Budget. Washington, D.C. Address of William D. Carey. Executive Assistant Director of the Bureau of the Budget at the 13th Federal Personnel Management Conference. San Francisco, CA. October 28, 1965.
- The Role of the Personnel Director in Management, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  Eric A. Nicol. Administrative Consultant. Bureau of the Budget. Executive Office of the President. Address given before the Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada. Cleveland, Ohio, October 1, 1940.
- Evaluation and Preservation of Official Personnel Folders, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  by U.S. Interagency records admin. conference. Report of Second Meeting, 1948-49 Season. October 13, 1948. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library.
- Business Management and Government, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  Roger Warren Jones. Bureau of the Budget, at the Executive Development Program, Cornell University, July 31, 1963.
- Basic Administrative Practice, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  Lawrence A. Apply Expect Consultant To Secretary of War. United States Department of Agriculture. Office of Personnel. Division of Training. 1941.